<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="GameRender.xsl"?>

<board-game>
    <games id="24">
        <images id="21">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic4314491_c7d6cb1e-808f-493c-92ef-0ec54dcd505c_1600x.jpg?v=1545067033</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/yggdrasil-new-edition-minor-damage</link>
        <maxPlayer>6</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>13</minAge>
        <minPlayer>1</minPlayer>
        <minTime>90</minTime>
        <ratingPoint>1</ratingPoint>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic4314491_c7d6cb1e-808f-493c-92ef-0ec54dcd505c_60x.jpg?v=1545067033</thumbnail>
        <title>Yggdrasil (New Edition) (Import) (Minor Damage)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="25">
        <description>InMangrovia, a light "gamer's game"/family game with a Caribbean mangrove setting, a clever role selection mechanism allows the players to choose two different bonuses/actions as well as the turn order in which they want these actions to be carried out — all by placing just one marker. Victory is achievable through a number of viable options, which guarantees high re-playability.The game is a fight over acquiring the best locations for your huts in this appealing and unspoiled landscape. If you manage to do so, you will become the rightful successor of the old chief and win the game. You gain Chief points by having the most huts (and the secondmost huts) along each of the eight divine paths monitored by the statues of Gods. Additional Chief points are earned by controlling sacred locations, by collecting amulets, and simply by building huts at lucrative spaces.Building a hut requires that the space's landscape is "active" and that you can pay the exact price (not overpay) for the space. Therefore, the game feels tight even from the very start. The game gets tighter and tighter towards the end of the game as you have fewer choices of spaces, and as the actions you choose become more and more crucial.In order to succeed in this game, you should carefully choose and time the best possible combination of actions, called "ritual sites". A boat goes from ritual site to ritual site, first on the west side, then on the east side (in opposite order), triggering each action. If, for instance, you choose a ritual site high up, you will have an early choice of cards, but a late choice of space to build your huts or to collect amulets (and vice versa). A fourth action type is to select "active landscapes" and become starting player, which makes it possible to control the next round. After all players have performed two actions, the round ends. The game is usually played over 10-14 rounds and ends when one player builds his last hut.Collecting amulets may be key in this game. Instead of keeping them as Chief points, you may use them to build huts on designated spaces which require payment in amulets instead of cards — and still to the exact price. Building huts on such spaces may be exactly what you need to get the majority along one or two divine paths. In order to gain enough amulets — and amulets of the appropriate values — you should position some of your huts on amulet spaces. The more huts you build on such spaces, the more amulets you can draw. The probability of getting the amulets you need will therefore increase.The game board is built as a matrix system, with some spaces being part of two divine paths while other spaces belong to just one. The spaces that are part of two divine paths are obviously most tempting, but can you afford to build your huts there?</description>
        <images id="23">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2251077_lg_1600x.png?v=1415905602</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/mangrovia</link>
        <maxPlayer>5</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>75</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2251077_lg_60x.png?v=1415905602</thumbnail>
        <title>Mangrovia</title>
    </games>
    <games id="26">
        <description>Note: This game is in German.  English rules is availablehere.This is not an expansion to Verräter, but an entirely new successor game toVerräter.With the highland pacified in Verräter, we now move to the ocean. Through bluff and strategy, players try to turn against the ship's captain, seizing the profits intended to be turned at the next port. Game includes a Pirate variant.</description>
        <images id="24">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Meuterer_1600x.jpg?v=1382846832</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/meuterer</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>12</minAge>
        <minPlayer>3</minPlayer>
        <minTime>60</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Meuterer_60x.jpg?v=1382846832</thumbnail>
        <title>Meuterer</title>
    </games>
    <games id="27">
        <description>Note: This game is in German, the but game itself is language independent.  English rules can be foundhere.In Thurn &amp;amp; Taxis, players build post office routes across Bavaria and the regions around, collecting bonus points in various ways. The board shows a map of all the cities, with roads leading from each one to some of its neighbors. There are various colored regions around the board, most with two or three cities, and a large region with all the Bavarian cities in the center.Players build postal routes from city to city to city so that each city is adjacent to the next city on the route and there is a road connecting these two cities. Each route must consist of at least three cities. Players may only build one route at a time. Routes are represented by melded city cards arranged in the order of the route.Players start with a supply of 20 post offices in their color, a carriage house card and a player aid card. The board is populated with bonus tiles, carriage cards and city cards. On a turn a player will draw a card from a display of six, face up, city cards (or the top of the face down deck) and meld one card, either starting a new route or adding to the current one. If after adding to the route, the length of the route is at least three cities, the player may declare it finished and score it. The player may, depending on the length of the route and which cities are in the route, place post offices in the cities, collect bonus tiles, and acquire a higher value carriage. Optionally, the player may receive support from one postal official in the form of: drawing a second card, melding a second card, refreshing the six city card display, or acquiring a higher value carriage than the route length when finishing a route. Once a route is scored the city cards of that route are discarded, and the player begins a new route on his next turn.When a player exhausts his supply of post offices or acquires a value 7 carriage the end of the game is triggered. Play continues until the player who is last in turn order finishes his turn, and the game ends. Players score points for their highest valued carriage and bonus tiles, and loose points for unplaced post offices. The player with the most points wins.The fact that you *must* add at least one city to your route each turn or lose the whole route gives the game an enjoyable planning element.</description>
        <images id="25">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic179923_lg_1600x.jpg?v=1412306452</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/thurn-and-taxis-import</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>13</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>60</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic179923_lg_60x.jpg?v=1412306452</thumbnail>
        <title>Thurn and Taxis (German Import)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="28">
        <images id="26">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic4314491_1600x.jpg?v=1545066462</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/yggdrasil</link>
        <maxPlayer>6</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>13</minAge>
        <minPlayer>1</minPlayer>
        <minTime>90</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic4314491_60x.jpg?v=1545066462</thumbnail>
        <title>Yggdrasil (New Edition) (Import)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="29">
        <description>Europe, 1347. A disaster is about to strike. The Black Death reaches Europe, and during the next 4-5 years, the population of Europe will be halved.The players settle in the various regions of Europe, while the plague spreads throughout all of the continent. The players gain help from the various classes of the middle ages: the Peasants provide population growth, the wise Monks keep the rats away, the rich Merchants flee when the plague approaches, the warfare conducted by the Knights spreads the plague to new areas, the Witches control the spread through magic and witchcraft, whereas the Kings avoid the plague by staying in their fortified palaces. But the plague does not make any distinction: when the rats arrive, no one can feel safe. When the plague withdraws and the game ends, the player with the highest surviving population wins.Rattus is a medium-strategy game that takes place in the Dark Ages during the black plague. The players try to hold off the disease.To do this they get help from farmers, magicians, knights, nobles, ... But nothing helps as long as the rats keep coming.February 2010: - 1st international version (Dutch/English/French and Norwegian) by White Goblin Games- 1st German version by Huch&amp;amp;Friends- 1st English version by Z-Man GamesThe international version will be available (mainly) in Benelux, France, and Norway. The German version will be available in Germany, Austria, and Switzerland.We expect that there will be localized versions (Italian, Spanish, etc.) later in 2010. Not decided yet.May 2010:Second international version by White Goblin GamesAugust 2010:Third international version by White Goblin GamesOctober 2010:First expansion for the game is called Pied Piper and is released at Essen 2010. The expansion was sold out in 2 days at the fair.Z-Man Games does an English version of the Pied Piper expansion, Axel does the Polish version of the Pied Piper expansion.January 2011:Fourth international version by White Goblin Games and second edition of the international Pied Piper expansion will be out in March 2011.Second English version by Z-Man Games will be out in March 2011.October 2011:Second expansion for the game called Rattus Africanus will be released at Essen 2011. Z-Man Games will release the first English edition of Rattus Africanus expansion also in october 2011.August 2012:Fifth international version by White Goblin Games will be out in August 2012. Second international version of the Africanus expansion will be released by White Goblin Games.April 2013:Second international version of the Pied Piper expansion will be released by White Goblin Games.</description>
        <images id="27">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Rattus_1600x.jpg?v=1395527303</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/rattus</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>45</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Rattus_60x.jpg?v=1395527303</thumbnail>
        <title>Rattus (Import)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="30">
        <description>Note: This game is in German.  The game itself is language independent.  English rules can be foundhere.Take Spades, and add evil. The result is Die Sieben Siegel.The game is a pretty standard trick-taking game. The cards are numbered 1-15 in five different suits, and red is always trump. If someone leads a color, you must follow suit if you can; otherwise, you can throw off a card or trump the trick. It's an exact-bidding game, but you predict your tricks by taking colored chips. For each trick that you win, you toss a chip back. If you take a trick in a color for which you didn't have a chip, then you must take a black chip (worth -3 points). If you have any colored chips left at the end of the round, they're worth -2 points. If you have any white chips left at the end of the round (wildcards that you get when someone takes a colored chip away from you during bidding), they're worth -4 points.There's also the saboteur, whose role is to feed unwanted tricks to other players. Instead of bidding tricks he takes 4 black chips. When players take tricks they didn't predict they take black chips from the saboteur. If the saboteur can feed enough of the black chips to enough players, he can zero out his score for that round. He gets -1 point for every black chip he has left at the end of the round.This is a mean-spirited game. Only play with people who can take it as such.</description>
        <images id="28">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic842146_1600x.jpg?v=1391393321</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/wizard-extreme</link>
        <maxPlayer>5</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>3</minPlayer>
        <minTime>30</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic842146_60x.jpg?v=1391393321</thumbnail>
        <title>Wizard Extreme (German Import)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="31">
        <description>Even for the mightiest pirates there comes a time when they must retire from their lives of invading and plunder — but what's coming afterward? Well, on the five peninsulas of Grog Island, they can invest their loot in rock-solid businesses, such as peg-leg shops, carpentries for figureheads, workshops for voodoo dolls, or the infamous "Grog Hole" pub.The core ofGrog Islandis its unique auction mechanism, which uses five colored dice. The players use these dice and the pips on them to create and raise bids. While the winner of an auction can claim buildings on certain peninsulas, the players who have passed are also rewarded: Not only do they receive goods like grog bottles or treasure maps but they also visit merchant ships where they can trade these goods for money, parrots or treasure chests. The auction mechanism ofGrog Islandmakes for tactical and interesting gameplay as in certain moments, passing can be almost as rewarding as winning an auction. Finding the right balance between bidding and backing out is the key to winning.The game ends as soon as one player has claimed a certain number of buildings, then all players score the secret goal cards they received both at the start of and during the game. These cards may give points for majorities on peninsulas as well as for claiming certain types of buildings or collecting certain goods. The player with the most points wins.</description>
        <images id="29">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Grog_Island_1600x.jpg?v=1415519929</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/grog-island</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>60</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Grog_Island_60x.jpg?v=1415519929</thumbnail>
        <title>Grog Island</title>
    </games>
    <games id="32">
        <images id="30">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2651468_1600x.jpg?v=1474145820</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/factory-funner</link>
        <maxPlayer>5</maxPlayer>
        <maxTime>40</maxTime>
        <minAge>11</minAge>
        <minPlayer>1</minPlayer>
        <minTime>20</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2651468_60x.jpg?v=1474145820</thumbnail>
        <title>Factory Funner</title>
    </games>
    <games id="33">
        <description>There's still much left to do in order to become the world's largest and most diverse amusement park! Your family (one of four) has a small, but steady income that should suffice to hire a few showmen to bring life to the oh-so-empty park site. As you earn more, you can afford a favor or two: the police officer is kinder to you, you can hire a migrant worker to do extra work, and you can even finagle the attention of a promoter or a journalist!The families will need to co-operate from time to time; after all, those grand attractions don't build themselves. In the end, the grand attractions are what will impress the crowds and bring about euphoric headlines in the newspapers!To set up Coney Island, each player takes two money tiles, a random building material and a player board, covering most of the spaces on that board with showmen tiles. At the start of each turn, a player receives income. At the beginning of the game a player's income is one VP, one money and one randomly drawn building material; as the game progresses, the player can remove showmen tiles to uncover VP, money and material spaces, thereby boosting his income. A player can never have more than five money tiles and five materials.A player then takes one to three main actions and up to five special actions:By spending two money, a player can acquire one of five character tiles (either from the supply or another player); each character provides a special action that the player can use each turn, such as spending money or VPs for material or buying newspaper tiles (which are worth points and can be spent for an additional action).Each main action may be executed at most once per turn unless extra actions are used from newspapers or from bonuses earned by placing certain building site tiles.After one player reaches 60 VP, and each player has had the same number of turns, the game ends, with players scoring their newspaper tiles and losing points for each showman on their player boards. The player with the most points wins.</description>
        <images id="31">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Coney_Island_1600x.jpg?v=1391372362</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/coney-island</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>60</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Coney_Island_60x.jpg?v=1391372362</thumbnail>
        <title>Coney Island</title>
    </games>
    <games id="34">
        <description>Note: This game is in French.The players act as traders trying to get victory points for building a network of offices, controlling cities, collecting bonus markers or for other traders using the cities they control. After controlling a line between two cities with your pawns you can decide to build an office (and maybe also establish control and/or get a bonus marker) or to get a skill improvement from some of the cities.Players have to improve their traders' "skills" for the following effects: getting more VP from offices in their network, getting more available action points, increasing the number of available pawns, and getting the right to place pawns and get more special pawns.</description>
        <images id="32">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Hansa_Teutonica_2ec1e9f2-545d-48e9-b971-e5665cc37fa2_1600x.jpg?v=1558114525</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/hansa-teutonica-french-edition</link>
        <maxPlayer>5</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>12</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>60</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Hansa_Teutonica_2ec1e9f2-545d-48e9-b971-e5665cc37fa2_60x.jpg?v=1558114525</thumbnail>
        <title>Hansa Teutonica (French Edition)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="35">
        <description>The year is 1252 and the great Kublai Khan has decided to build his summer palace. He has searched for the best architects who are looking to win fame and prestige — and sometimes you have to harm other architects' prestige to step forward...Xanadúis a highly interactive card game for 2 to 5 players. Cards can be buildings with four squares of available resources that can be used by any player (including the owner of the card). To be able to retrieve and use those resources, the players assign workers, which are also cards.  The players compete to earn the most "tong baos", the money in the game, by selling the constructions to the Khan.Xanadúis a strategy game of building and sabotage, for casual and experienced players. </description>
        <images id="33">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2529078_lg_1600x.jpg?v=1452670769</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/xanadu</link>
        <maxPlayer>5</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>13</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>50</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2529078_lg_60x.jpg?v=1452670769</thumbnail>
        <title>Xanadú</title>
    </games>
    <games id="36">
        <description>Mü is regarded by many as one of the best offerings in the trick-taking genre. Players reveal cards to declare their bids: the highest bidder becomes the Chief and the second highest bidder is the Vice. Both the Vice and Chief choose a trump (either number or suit), and then players try to capture tricks to score the most points. The Chief chooses a partner and tries to cover the bid to score bonus points, while the Vice and remaining players seek to stop the Chief from reaching his goal.The deck consists of 60 cards in 5 different colored suits. Each suit contains cards numbered from 0 to 9, with two of each the 1 and 7 cards. Cards also have 0, 1, or 2 triangles printed on them to show the point value of that card.Mü &amp;amp; Lots More includes a a tweaked version of Mü and a different set of games.</description>
        <images id="34">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic702307_lg_1600x.jpg?v=1392494736</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/mu-more</link>
        <maxPlayer>8</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>12</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>60</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic702307_lg_60x.jpg?v=1392494736</thumbnail>
        <title>Mü &amp; More (German Import)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="37">
        <images id="35">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Verrater_1600x.jpg?v=1391373417</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/verrater</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>12</minAge>
        <minPlayer>3</minPlayer>
        <minTime>60</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Verrater_60x.jpg?v=1391373417</thumbnail>
        <title>Verräter</title>
    </games>
    <games id="38">
        <description>Note: This game is in German.  A few paste up can be foundhere.  English rules can be foundhere.After the immediate response to Richard Breese's Keydom at Essen 1999, Hans im Glück Verlags-GmbH contracted to take the basic game idea and produce a version of the game. Aladdin's Dragons, or Morgenland in the original German, is the product of their cooperation.The game features players putting numbered bidding chips face-down onto the board sequentially. After the players have placed all of their chips, then each of the areas is resolved. The bottom part of the board is where players attempt to gather treasure tokens, which is the overall currency of the game. The middle part of the board features a number of special actions, which help the players cast spells, trade in their resource tokens, or block other players' actions. The top part of the board is where players use treasure tokens to purchase artifacts, and the player who can collect the most artifacts by the end of the game will be the victor.Won Games Magazine Game of the Year award in 2001.</description>
        <images id="36">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic1058394_lg_1600x.jpg?v=1498542301</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/aladdin-s-dragons</link>
        <maxPlayer>5</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>3</minPlayer>
        <minTime>90</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic1058394_lg_60x.jpg?v=1498542301</thumbnail>
        <title>Morgenland (aka Aladdin's Dragons) (German Import)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="39">
        <images id="37">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic3167080_027e1871-d4e4-4fc6-a043-8bccfb53e879_1600x.png?v=1489768632</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/kepler-3042-minor-damage</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <maxTime>90</maxTime>
        <minAge>14</minAge>
        <minPlayer>1</minPlayer>
        <minTime>60</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic3167080_027e1871-d4e4-4fc6-a043-8bccfb53e879_60x.png?v=1489768632</thumbnail>
        <title>Kepler-3042 (Minor Damage)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="40">
        <images id="38">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2855602_1600x.jpg?v=1474144622</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/kigi</link>
        <maxPlayer>5</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>20</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2855602_60x.jpg?v=1474144622</thumbnail>
        <title>Bonsai (German Import)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="41">
        <description>Note: This game is in FrenchTikal is a game of exploration within the Central American jungles in search of lost temples and the treasures within. Players send their team of explorers into the jungle, exposing more and more of the terrain. Along the way, you find temples that require further uncovering and treasures. Players attempt to score points for occupying temples and holding onto treasure.Tikal is the first game of the Mask Trilogy. </description>
        <images id="39">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2909347_f06c2824-2e2e-487b-90bd-70ca7b311d09_1600x.png?v=1481554450</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/tikal-french-import-minor-damage</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>120</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2909347_f06c2824-2e2e-487b-90bd-70ca7b311d09_60x.png?v=1481554450</thumbnail>
        <title>Tikal (French) (Minor Damage)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="42">
        <images id="40">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2834112_lg_1600x.png?v=1474143541</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/battalia-the-creation</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <maxTime>180</maxTime>
        <minAge>13</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>60</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2834112_lg_60x.png?v=1474143541</thumbnail>
        <title>BATTALIA: The Creation (German Import)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="43">
        <images id="41">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Sumeria_1600x.jpg?v=1398060244</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/sumeria</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>3</minPlayer>
        <minTime>45</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Sumeria_60x.jpg?v=1398060244</thumbnail>
        <title>Sumeria</title>
    </games>
    <games id="44">
        <description>The balance of power is shifting among theOrder Of The Gods!Play these new tiles with theVöluspábase game, or blend tiles from theOrder of the Godsexpansion with tiles from theSaga of Eddaexpansion. Four recommended game set-up variants are included, and many other variants are possible, enabling you to enjoyVöluspáand these expansions in many different ways. The possibilities inVöluspáare more endless than ever!</description>
        <images id="42">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic1703132_1600x.jpg?v=1536695728</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/voluspa-order-of-the-gods</link>
        <maxPlayer>5</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>45</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic1703132_60x.jpg?v=1536695728</thumbnail>
        <title>Völuspá: Order of the Gods (White Goblin Games New Edition)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="45">
        <description>The King is dead! Cardis has fallen...After a long siege, the empire of Asmidan has conquered Cardis and the Conclave of Law has been sent by the Emperor to establish the new rule. The city is in disarray and several factions struggle for power behind the scenes. The former Queen is using her influence to gather allies in an effort to help her son claim the throne. The Order of the Coin — a group of wealthy individuals — wants to rise to power ensuring the gold keeps flowing. The Asmidan's Church desires to seize control of the newly conquered city by using the feared Inquisition to sway whoever opposes it.In Shadows over the Empire, players take the role of leaders of four factions in a struggle for control of Cardis. They must influence various personalities and have them do their bidding. Loyalties are constantly changing and great allies become mortal enemies in a city filled with desire for dominion. Who will prevail?</description>
        <images id="43">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Shadows_over_the_Empire_1600x.jpg?v=1394911320</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/shadows-over-the-empire</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>12</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>90</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Shadows_over_the_Empire_60x.jpg?v=1394911320</thumbnail>
        <title>Shadows over the Empire</title>
    </games>
    <games id="46">
        <images id="44">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic4021507_1600x.jpg?v=1520435976</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/civilization</link>
        <maxPlayer>7</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>12</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>360</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic4021507_60x.jpg?v=1520435976</thumbnail>
        <title>Civilization (Gibsons Edition)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="47">
        <images id="45">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic3018118_1600x.jpg?v=1491446479</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/squirrel-rush</link>
        <maxPlayer>6</maxPlayer>
        <maxTime>30</maxTime>
        <minAge>6</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>15</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic3018118_60x.jpg?v=1491446479</thumbnail>
        <title>Squirrel Rush</title>
    </games>
    <games id="48">
        <images id="46">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2606432_1600x.jpg?v=1474145542</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/kumo-hogosha</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <maxTime>30</maxTime>
        <minAge>8</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>25</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2606432_60x.jpg?v=1474145542</thumbnail>
        <title>KUMO Hogosha</title>
    </games>
    <games id="49">
        <description> Note: This game is in Polish.  The game itself is language independent.  English rules can be found here.Welcome to Santiago, the second largest city in Cuba, home of legendary rum and birthplace of the revolution! The chaotic streets hum with the sounds of bustling crowds and busy commerce. Cargo ships constantly arrive and depart from the port. Demand is continuous, if unpredictable, for a supply of local products such as exotic fruits, sugar, rum, tobacco, and cigars.In Santiago de Cuba, your business card says "broker", but in reality you're a shady wheeler-dealer who arranges deals with the locals and with corruptible officials to move goods and meet the demand of those ever-present cargo ships – and your ability to procure these goods is only as reliable as your "connections".At the start of the game, nine locals – the Cubans – are randomly arranged on a path around Santiago, with the port being the tenth location on the circuit. Each Cuban has a different ability: e.g., give a player two tobacco, give a player a good of his choice, force opponents to give you something, give money or victory points (VPs), and seize a building or allow a player to use a previously seized building. What are these buildings? At the start of the game, twelve buildings are randomly placed on the game board in four color-coded groups (white, yellow, etc.) of three. As with the Cubans, these buildings give players a special ability when used: convert tobacco to cigars, change VPs to money or vica versa, increase the value of goods delivered to the ship, render a Cuban inactive for the next round, and so on.Players will deliver goods to seven ships throughout the course of the game. The demand for each ship is determined via a die roll; the active player rolls five dice – one for each type of good – then chooses four of the values rolled to represent demand for goods of the same color as the die.All players share a car and travel around the island together. On a turn, the active player can move the car to the next location on the path (whether Cuban or port) for free, or pay one peso for each spot moved beyond that. After taking a Cuban action, the player then must move his player piece to a building of the same color as the flower on that Cuban. If he takes an action in a building owned by someone else, that player earns 1 VP. (One Cuban allows a player to use the same building where his piece is currently located.)If a player moves to port, players take turns delivering all goods of one type to the ship to meet demand, adjusting the demand dice as needed. A player earns 2-4 VP for each good delivered; a player doesn't have to deliver goods. If the ship's demand isn't met after everyone delivers or passes, the VP bounty per good is increased by one and the ship remains in place – unless the value was already at 4 VP, in which case the ship sails. In this case, or when all the demand is met, a new ship comes into port with new demand values.After seven ships have sailed, the players earn 1 VP for every three goods still on hand, then tally their VPs. The player with the most VPs wins, with ties broken by goods remaining, then money.Each game poses new tactical challenges for the players, thanks to ever-changing combinations of buildings, Cuban inhabitants and demand for goods.</description>
        <images id="47">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic1522226_1600x.jpg?v=1505364984</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/santiago-de-cuba-1</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>12</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>60</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic1522226_60x.jpg?v=1505364984</thumbnail>
        <title>Santiago de Cuba (Polish Import)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="50">
        <images id="48">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic3120939_1600x.jpg?v=1500085521</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/paimiahhh</link>
        <maxTime>40</maxTime>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>4</minPlayer>
        <minTime>25</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic3120939_60x.jpg?v=1500085521</thumbnail>
        <title>PaiMiahhh</title>
    </games>
    <games id="51">
        <images id="49">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic259380_1600x.jpg?v=1522384557</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/gipsy-king</link>
        <maxPlayer>5</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>8</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>30</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic259380_60x.jpg?v=1522384557</thumbnail>
        <title>Gipsy King</title>
    </games>
    <games id="52">
        <description>Note: This game is in German.  But the game itself is language independent.  English rules can be foundhere.By entering into and then breaking-off alliances Samurai, Shogun and Daimyo fight for the most valuable booty. Only with power and decision can you accomplish your goal before the outbreak of revolution! A game of negotiation and bluff for merciless Ronins.Microbadge: Oriente fan</description>
        <images id="50">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic57808_1600x.jpg?v=1474139182</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/oriente</link>
        <maxPlayer>12</maxPlayer>
        <maxTime>30</maxTime>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>4</minPlayer>
        <minTime>20</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic57808_60x.jpg?v=1474139182</thumbnail>
        <title>Oriente (German Import)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="53">
        <images id="51">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic243490_md_1600x.jpg?v=1431969921</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/tyranno-ex</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>12</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>120</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic243490_md_60x.jpg?v=1431969921</thumbnail>
        <title>Tyranno Ex</title>
    </games>
    <games id="54">
        <description>In Drum Roll each player takes over the role of a circus owner in the early 1900s. Each player moves around Europe hiring performers and giving shows.There are five main categories of performers: the Tamers, the Acrobats, the Bizarre, the Magicians, and the Jugglers. Each of them have different demands the player must fulfill in order to give their best performance.The requirements, which vary between performers, are Rehearsal, Equipment, Supplies, Costumes, and Promotion. There are three levels of performances that each performer can end up doing in a show: a poor one, a good one, and an outstanding one. The higher the level of performance, the more requirements each performer will have to fulfill in order to achieve it.The better the performance, the more each player can get out of it. When performers do outstanding performances, the player must choose between getting the maximum amount of benefit out of them, or getting the Prestige Points they are offering. There are also other ways to improve a circus such as trailers, investments, and personnel that will help your performers do their best.</description>
        <images id="52">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Drum_Roll_077072c7-ff2a-4b0d-815b-e5d37422f768_1600x.jpg?v=1428643376</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/drum-roll-minor-damage</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>12</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>90</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Drum_Roll_077072c7-ff2a-4b0d-815b-e5d37422f768_60x.jpg?v=1428643376</thumbnail>
        <title>Drum Roll (Minor Damage)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="55">
        <description>There's still much left to do in order to become the world's largest and most diverse amusement park! Your family (one of four) has a small, but steady income that should suffice to hire a few showmen to bring life to the oh-so-empty park site. As you earn more, you can afford a favor or two: the police officer is kinder to you, you can hire a migrant worker to do extra work, and you can even finagle the attention of a promoter or a journalist!The families will need to co-operate from time to time; after all, those grand attractions don't build themselves. In the end, the grand attractions are what will impress the crowds and bring about euphoric headlines in the newspapers!To set up Coney Island, each player takes two money tiles, a random building material and a player board, covering most of the spaces on that board with showmen tiles. At the start of each turn, a player receives income. At the beginning of the game a player's income is one VP, one money and one randomly drawn building material; as the game progresses, the player can remove showmen tiles to uncover VP, money and material spaces, thereby boosting his income. A player can never have more than five money tiles and five materials.A player then takes one to three main actions and up to five special actions:By spending two money, a player can acquire one of five character tiles (either from the supply or another player); each character provides a special action that the player can use each turn, such as spending money or VPs for material or buying newspaper tiles (which are worth points and can be spent for an additional action).Each main action may be executed at most once per turn unless extra actions are used from newspapers or from bonuses earned by placing certain building site tiles.After one player reaches 60 VP, and each player has had the same number of turns, the game ends, with players scoring their newspaper tiles and losing points for each showman on their player boards. The player with the most points wins.</description>
        <images id="53">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Coney_Island_67dd2c53-111c-4454-a80a-416934da56b9_1600x.jpg?v=1433821931</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/coney-island-minor-damage</link>
        <maxPlayer>4</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>60</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Coney_Island_67dd2c53-111c-4454-a80a-416934da56b9_60x.jpg?v=1433821931</thumbnail>
        <title>Coney Island (Minor Damage)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="56">
        <description>Note: This game is in GermanIn Citadels, players take on new roles each round to represent characters they hire in order to help them acquire gold and erect buildings. The game ends at the close of a round in which a player erects her eighth building. Players then tally their points, and the player with the highest score wins.Players start with a number of building cards in their hand; buildings come in five colors, with the purple buildings typically having a special ability and the other colored buildings providing a benefit when you play particular characters. At the start of each round, the player who was king the previous round discards one of the eight character cards at random, chooses one, then passes the cards to the next player, etc. until each player has secretly chosen a character. Each character has a special ability, and the usefulness of any character depends upon your situation, and that of your opponents. The characters then carry out their actions in numerical order: the assassin eliminating another character for the round, the thief stealing all gold from another character, the wizard swapping building cards with another player, the warlord optionally destroys a building in play, and so on.On a turn, a player earns two or more gold (or draws two building cards then discards one), then optionally constructs one building (or up to three if playing the architect this round). Buildings cost gold equal to the number of symbols on them, and each building is worth a certain number of points. In addition to points from buildings, at the end of the game a player scores bonus points for having eight buildings or buildings of all five colors.</description>
        <images id="54">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic953739_lg_1_1600x.jpg?v=1431969418</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/ohne-furcht-und-adel-aka-citadel-german-edition</link>
        <maxPlayer>7</maxPlayer>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>60</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic953739_lg_1_60x.jpg?v=1431969418</thumbnail>
        <title>Ohne Furcht und Adel (aka Citadel) (German Edition)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="57">
        <images id="55">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2730244_1600x.jpg?v=1474143053</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/achaia</link>
        <maxPlayer>5</maxPlayer>
        <maxTime>90</maxTime>
        <minAge>14</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>60</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/pic2730244_60x.jpg?v=1474143053</thumbnail>
        <title>Achaia</title>
    </games>
    <games id="58">
        <description>Sukkubeis an abstract game in which each player represents a character of the circus: The Tamer, the Lion, the Presenter, the Clown, the Strong Man, and the Dancer. If fewer than six players are in the game, assign the remaining positions to the "bots", which will play automatically.They are distributed, discoveries, five cards to each character.The cards are played according to the rules.These cards allow to rotate the cube, which is nothing other than the box itself of the game.When any character ends his cards, or can not play any according to the rules, the round ends and the character on the upper face of the cube (the Dominator) earns a point. You rotate the cube of 180 degrees and the character that was at the bottom end of the previous round (the Sukkube) is the first to play in the new run. First player to reach 5 points Wins.The game will test the predictive power of the players, having played all cards on the table.Seven play variants let you experience different moods.</description>
        <images id="56">
            <imageUrl>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Untitled_d12fb908-7c03-4d0e-94e7-e9d2f1c38408_1600x.png?v=1455430032</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamebliss.com//collections/all/products/sukkube</link>
        <maxPlayer>6</maxPlayer>
        <maxTime>50</maxTime>
        <minAge>10</minAge>
        <minPlayer>1</minPlayer>
        <minTime>25</minTime>
        <thumbnail>//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0274/9631/products/Untitled_d12fb908-7c03-4d0e-94e7-e9d2f1c38408_60x.png?v=1455430032</thumbnail>
        <title>Sukkube</title>
    </games>
    <games id="59">
        <category>Game nhập vai</category>
        <description>TrongDescent: Journeys in the Dark (Second Edition)người chơi sẽ vào vai bốn anh hùng dũng cảm đương đầu với một người làm overlord. Mỗi game sẽ là một cuộc phiêu lưu đến những hang động bí ẩn, dấu tích cổ xưa, cánh rừng bị nguyền rủa để chiến đấu với các loại quái vật để nhận được phần thưởng và ngăn chặn overlord thực hiện mưu đồ bá chủ của hắn.Khi mà nguy hiểm ở khắp mọi nơi, chiến đấu là điều không thể tránh.Descent: Journeys in the Dark (Second Edition)sử dụng cơ chế đổ xúc xắc riêng biệt. Người chơi sử dụng những xúc xắc này theo khả năng của nhân vật, vũ khí sử dụng và chúng đều có những hiệu ứng khác nhau. Tận dụng mọi lợi thế có được là con đường ngắn nhất dẫn đến chiến thắng.Bao gồm những board 2 mặt để thể hiện bản đồ, nhiều anh hùng với những kỹ năng khác nhau và một cốt truyện tương đối hoành tráng,Descent: Journeys in the Dark (Second Edition)sẽ đưa bạn vào thế giới fantasy đầy mê hoặc để hợp sức chiến thắng cái ác.</description>
        <images id="57">
            <imageUrl>https://i0.wp.com/www.boardgamehub.net/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/descent-1.jpg?resize=495%2C400&amp;ssl=1</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamehub.net/descent-journeys-in-the-dark-second-edition/</link>
        <minAge>14</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>120</minTime>
        <thumbnail>https://i2.wp.com/www.boardgamehub.net/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/descent-7.jpg?fit=600%2C600&amp;ssl=1</thumbnail>
        <title>Descent: Journeys in the Dark (Second Edition)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="60">
        <category>Game nhập vai</category>
        <description>TrongWar of the Ring, một người chơi điều khiển liên minh tự do (Free People), người chơi khác nắm giữ quân đoàn bóng tối (Shadow Armies). Tuy nhiên, các nước trong liên minh tự do không quá mặn mà với việc gây hấn với Sauron. Chỉ khi bị tấn công hoặc thuyết phục bởi Gandalf hoặc các thành viên trong đoàn hộ nhẫn thì những nước này mới sẵn sàng chiến đấu.Người chơi có thể dành chiến thắng game thông qua điểm quân sự, khi Sauron chiếm đóng được một số lượng các thành trì của liên minh tự do và ngược lại. Niềm hy vọng lớn nhất của liên minh tự do đặt ở đoàn hộ nhẫn. Trong khi những chận chiến nảy lửa xảy ra tại khắp trung địa, đoàn hộ nhẫn bí mật mang chiến nhẫn thần đến Mount Doom để thiêu hủy. Tuy nhiên, Sauron biết được điều này và sẽ liên tục tìm kiếm cũng như gây ra muôn vàn khó khăn cho người chơi. Game sử dụng cơ chế the Hunt để minh họa cho những sự kiện này.Bắt đầu mỗi vòng đấu, 2 người chơi đổ xúc xắc để xác định những hành động thực hiên bao gồm (di chuyển quân đội, anh hùng, chiêu mộ lính, tăng cường ảnh hưởng. Ngoài ra,War of the Ringcòn sử dụng các action card như một yếu tố bất ngờ. Những thẻ bài này mô phỏng một sự kiện có thật trong truyện và có thể xoay chuyển cục diện chiến trường ngay lập tức. Một wargame lấy bối cảnh fantasy của Lord of the Ring thay vì chiến tranh thế giới đã thổi một làn gió mới vào danh sách có phần hơi khô khan của wargame cổ điển.</description>
        <images id="58">
            <imageUrl>https://i0.wp.com/www.boardgamehub.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/warofthering-2.jpg?resize=495%2C400&amp;ssl=1</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamehub.net/war-of-the-ring-second-edition/</link>
        <minAge>13</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>150</minTime>
        <thumbnail>https://i1.wp.com/www.boardgamehub.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/warofthering-4.jpg?fit=705%2C478&amp;ssl=1</thumbnail>
        <title>War of the Ring (second edition)</title>
    </games>
    <games id="61">
        <category>Game nhập vai</category>
        <description>Mansions Of Madnesslà kết hợp của nhiều cốt truyện khác nhau, mỗi cốt truyện lại có 1 bản đồ và yếu tố khác nhau, thay đổi để người chơi không nhàm chán, qua đó được chia thành 2 phe, một phe là những Người Thám Hiểm phải thực hiện nhiệm vụ mà phe đối thủ, ở đây là Người Canh Cửa đưa ra. Trò chơi có những yếu tố nhập vai như giải đố, thu lượm đồ, chiến đấu,….chắc chắn sẽ giúp người chơi ở cả 2 phe cảm thấy thú vị. Điểm nổi bật nữa là mô hình của game rất đa dạng và được sản xuất rất tốt, một đặc điểm dễ thường thấy của hãng Fantasy Flight.</description>
        <images id="59">
            <imageUrl>https://i2.wp.com/www.boardgamehub.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/mansions-of-madness-13.jpg?resize=495%2C400&amp;ssl=1</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamehub.net/mansions-of-madness/</link>
        <minAge>13</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>120</minTime>
        <thumbnail>https://i1.wp.com/www.boardgamehub.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/mansions-of-madness-11.jpg?fit=705%2C705&amp;ssl=1</thumbnail>
        <title>Mansions of Madness</title>
    </games>
    <games id="62">
        <category>Game nhập vai</category>
        <description>Trong game, mỗi người chơi đóng vai 1Mage Knight, là các hiệp sĩ thần thánh luôn tìm kiếm quyền lực và sức mạnh. Sứ mệnh củaMage Knighttrong game là khám phá và chinh phục vùng đất mà đế chế Atlantean kiểm soát. Bạn phải xây dựng bộ thẻ bài hành động của mình bằng các phép thuật mạnh mẽ, các hành động cấp cao; đồng thời xây dựng đội quân của mình bằng cách tuyển thêm lính tráng trong các làng, các thành… để từ đó có đủ sức mạnh để chinh phục các thành phố lớn nhất trong game. Người chiến thắng là người có danh tiếng cao nhất (fame).Với cách chơi kết hợp thể loại nhập vai, sưu tập bài (deckbuilding) và thể loại board game truyền thống (Mage Knightcó bản đồ riêng), Mage Knight là 1 board game sáng tạo, thể hiện được cốt truyện sâu và cách chơi rất riêng, xứng đáng có 1 chỗ trong tủ game của bạn.</description>
        <images id="60">
            <imageUrl>https://i1.wp.com/www.boardgamehub.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/mageknightboardgame-3.jpg?resize=495%2C400&amp;ssl=1</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamehub.net/mage-knight-board-game/</link>
        <minAge>14</minAge>
        <minPlayer>1</minPlayer>
        <minTime>150</minTime>
        <thumbnail>https://i0.wp.com/www.boardgamehub.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/mageknightboardgame-2.jpg?fit=705%2C503&amp;ssl=1</thumbnail>
        <title>Mage Knight Board Game</title>
    </games>
    <games id="63">
        <category>Game nhập vai</category>
        <description>Merchants &amp;#038; Marauderskể về cuộc đời của một thương gia nổi tiếng hay một tên hải tặc đáng sợ ở vùng biển Caribbean trong suốt thời đại vàng son của cướp biển. Game kể câu chuyện của những con người tìm kiếm vận may thông qua buôn bán, săn tin đồn, thực hiện nhiệm vụ, và tất nhiên là cả cướp bóc. Và họ không thể thực hiện được những chiến tích lừng danh nếu thiếu một con tàu dũng mãnh với hàng tá khẩu pháo sẵn sàng nã những làn đạn chết người, và một nhóm thủy thủ trung thành, sẵn sàng hy sinh vì đồng đội. Thuyền trưởng anh hùng nào sẽ đạt được vinh quang, giàu có, danh tiếng lẫy lừng và ai sẽ phải bỏ xác dưới đáy biển sâu thăm thẳm, hãy đến vớiMerchants &amp;#038; Maraudersđể trải nghiệm tất cả những điều đó!TrongMerchants và Marauders, người chơi sẽ vào vai thuyền trưởng của một con tàu *nhỏ* ở vùng Caribbean. Nhiệm vụ của người chơi là kiếm điểm danh vọng (cướp biển cũng cần phải có tiếng tăm) từ việc hoàn thành những chiến tích để đời (thông qua hoàn thành nhiệm vụ khó khăn hoặc giải mã tin đồn), nghiền nát kẻ thù không đội trời chung (thông qua việc đánh bại các đối thủ và NPC trong chiến đấu), tích lũy vàng bạc châu báu, thực hiện một phi vụ cướp bóc hoặc buôn bán hoành tráng và nâng cấp chiến thuyền của mình. Trong khi điểm thu được từ việc thực hiện các nhiệm vụ khác nhau là vĩnh viễn, điểm từ tích lũy vàng có thể bị cướp hoặc mất nếu thuyền trưởng bị chết. Tuy nhiên đây cũng chính là yếu tố bất ngờ của trò chơi. Người chơi đầu tiên tích lũy được 10 điểm danh vọng chiến thắng game.Câu hỏi lớn nhất đối với người chơi là phải lựa chọn giữa con đường chính đạo (thương nhân) đầy gian nan hay tà đạo (hải tặc) nhiều rủ ro. Hải tặc luôn bị săn đuổi bởi các tàu hải quân các nước hay bởi chính những người chơi khác đơn giản vì tiền thưởng truy nã quá hậu hĩnh đồng thời gặp nhiều khó khăn trong việc tuồn hàng. Tuy nhiên, lợi ích từ việc cướp bóc đem lại quá ngon lành và ngoài ra bạn lại còn được đóng vai kẻ xấu nữa (khà khà). Trong khi đó, các thương nhân cũng lo lắng khi bị săn đuổi bởi những tên cướp biển và thường phải hy sinh khả năng chiến đấu của tàu để chứa hàng hóa. Bù lại, họ thường được bảo kê bởi những tàu chiến cỡ bự bao gồm cảMan o’ Warđủ để hù mấy tên cướp biển cong đuôi chạy.Merchants &amp;#038; Marauderslà game mô phỏng cướp biển cực kỳ vui nhộn và phong phú về mặt nội dung. Thời gian chơi của game khá ngắn, rất thích hợp chơi vào các buổi tối tụ họp gia đình và bạn bè.</description>
        <images id="61">
            <imageUrl>https://i1.wp.com/www.boardgamehub.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/merchantsmarauders-8.jpg?resize=495%2C400&amp;ssl=1</imageUrl>
        </images>
        <link>https://www.boardgamehub.net/merchants-marauders/</link>
        <minAge>13</minAge>
        <minPlayer>2</minPlayer>
        <minTime>180</minTime>
        <thumbnail>https://i0.wp.com/www.boardgamehub.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/merchantsmarauders.jpg?fit=705%2C705&amp;ssl=1</thumbnail>
        <title>Merchants &amp;#038; Marauders</title>
    </games>
</board-game>
